I’m like some kind of Supernova
Watch out
Look at me go Look at me go
재미 좀 볼 재미 좀 볼
ちょっと面白くなる
Gon' have a ball
빛의 Core
光の Core
Light at the Core
So hot hot hot, hot hot hot hot
문이 열려
扉が開く
Open the door
서로의 존재를 느껴
お互いの存在を感じる
Feelin' each other's presence
마치 Discord
まるで Discord
Like a Discord
날 닮은 너 너 누구야
私に似た君 君は誰？
My lookalike, who are you?
(Drop)
사건은 다가와 Ah Oh Ay
事件は近づいて来る Ah Oh Ay
Event's imminent Ah Oh Ay
거세게 커져가 Ah Oh Ay
激しく大きくなっていく Ah Oh Ay
Blowin' up crazy Ah Oh Ay
That tick that tick tick bomb
감히 건드리지 못할 걸
恐れ多くて手も触れられないはず
Won't dare touch it
(누구도 말이야)
(誰もね)
(No one ever will)
지금 내 안에선
いま私の中では
Right now it's inside me
Su su su Supernova
Nova aespa!
Can’t stop hyperstellar aespa!
원초 그걸 찾아
原初 それを探して
Seek its origin
Bring the light of a dying star
불러낸 내 우주를 봐 봐
呼び出した私の宇宙を見てみて
Watch this universe I've brought out
Supernova
Ah Body bang bang bang bang bang
Make it feel too right
휩쓸린 에너지 It’s so special
押し流されたエネルギー It’s so special
Swept-up energy, It's so special
잔인한 Queen 이며 Scene 이자 종결
残忍な Queenであり Sceneであり終結
Cruel Queen and the Scene, its finale
이토록 거대한 내 안의 Explosion
こんなにも巨大な私の中の Explosion
It's massive, this Explosion within me
내 모든 세포 별로부터 만들어져
私の全細胞 星から作られる
Every one of my cells are created from stars
(Under my control Ah)
질문은 계속돼 Ah Oh Ay
質問は続く Ah Oh Ay
Questions keep comin' Ah Oh Ay
우린 어디서 왔나 Oh Ay
我々はどこから来たのか Oh Ay
Where did we come from Oh Ay
>느껴 내 안에선
感じる 私の中では
Feel it in me
Su su su Supernova
Nova aespa!
Can’t stop hyperstellar aespa!
원초 그걸 찾아
原初 それを探して
Seek its origin
Bring the light of a dying star
불러낸 내 우주를 봐 봐
呼び出した私の宇宙を見てみて
Watch this universe I've brought out
Supernova
보이지 않는 힘으로
見えない力で
With my invisible force
네게 손 내밀어 볼까
君に手を差し伸べてみようかな
Should I reach out my hand to you
가능한 모든 가능성
可能なすべての可能性
All the possible possibilities
무한 속의 너를 만나
無限の中の君に出逢う
Meeting you inside infinity
It’s about to bang bang
Don’t forget my name
Su su su Supernova
사건은 다가와 Ah Oh Ay
事件は近づいて来る Ah Oh Ay
Event's imminent Ah Oh Ay
거세게 커져가 Ah Oh Ay
激しく大きくなっていく Ah Oh Ay
Blowin' up crazy Ah Oh Ay
질문은 계속돼 Ah Oh Ay
質問は続く Ah Oh Ay
Questions keep comin' Ah Oh Ay
우린 어디서 왔나 Oh Ay
我々はどこから来たのか Oh Ay
Where did we come from Oh Ay
사건은 다가와 Ah Oh Ay
事件は近づいて来る Ah Oh Ay
Event's imminent Ah Oh Ay
거세게 커져가 Ah Oh Ay
激しく大きくなっていく Ah Oh Ay
Blowin' up crazy Ah Oh Ay
Tell me, tell me, tell me Oh Ay
우린 어디서 왔나 Oh Ay
我々はどこから来たのか Oh Ay
Where did we come from Oh Ay
우린 어디서 왔나 Oh Ay
我々はどこから来たのか Oh Ay
Where did we come from Oh Ay
Nova (Nova)
Can’t stop hyperstellar aespa!
원초 그걸 찾아
原初 それを探して
Seek its origin
Bring the light of a dying star
불러낸 내 우주를 봐 봐
呼び出した私の宇宙を見てみて
Watch this universe I've brought out
Super Hey! nova Ha!
사건은 다가와 Ah Oh Ay
事件は近づいて来る Ah Oh Ay
Event's imminent Ah Oh Ay
거세게 커져가 Ah Oh Ay
激しく大きくなっていく Ah Oh Ay
Blowin' up crazy Ah Oh Ay
질문은 계속돼 Ah Oh Ay
質問は続く Ah Oh Ay
Questions keep comin' Ah Oh Ay
우린 어디서 왔나 Oh Ay
我々はどこから来たのか Oh Ay
Where did we come from Oh Ay
사건은 다가와 Ah Oh Ay
事件は近づいて来る Ah Oh Ay
Event's imminent Ah Oh Ay
거세게 커져가 Ah Oh Ay
激しく大きくなっていく Ah Oh Ay
Blowin' up crazy Ah Oh Ay
질문은 계속돼 Ah Oh Ay
質問は続く Ah Oh Ay
Questions keep comin' Ah Oh Ay
Bring the light of a dying star
Supernova